Guide to the ethnic archives oral histories audio recordings 1966-1997
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- Westwood oral history project, 1987
  - Session 22, 1987 May 07; Compact disc (Disc WW-3)
  - Session 23, undated; Compact disc (Disc WW-4)
  - Unknown oral history, undated; Compact disc (Disc WW-5)
  - Session 21, 1987 May 06; Compact disc (Disc WW-6)
  - Session 22, undated; Compact disc (Disc WW-7)
  - Session 23, undated; Compact disc (Disc WW-8)
- Krodel interviews, undated
  - Marjorie Lee Krodel, undated; Compact disc (Disc Krodel A)
  - Marjorie Lee Krodel, undated; Compact disc (Disc Krodel B)
  - Marjorie Lee Krodel, undated; Compact disc (Disc Krodel C)
  - Marjorie Lee Krodel, undated; Compact disc (Disc Krodel)
- WRPT oral histories, 1974
  - Edna Jones, Ed Johnson, undated; Compact disc (Disc WRPT-WR-7)
  - Mary Wilson Schurz, undated; Compact disc (Disc WRPT-WR-17)
    History of Nevada.
  - Popeye McCloud, 1974 March 12; Compact disc (Disc WRPT-WR-18)
  - Roy Higgins, 1974 February 14; Compact disc (Disc WRPT-WR-23)
    Painted Rocks.
- Indian self-rule oral histories, 1983-1984
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-101A)
    KUER and The Institute of the American West.
    Speaker Floyd O'Neil.
    The Indian New Deal
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-102-1A)
    Panel: The Indian New Deal
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-102-2A)
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-103-1A)
    Panel: John Collier, Felix Cohen and adoption of the I.R.A.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-103-2A)
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-104-1A)
    Panel: Implementing the I.R.A.: The B.I.A. record under John Collier.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-104-2A)
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-105-1A)
    Panel: I.R.A. Governments
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISP-105-2A)
    Panel: I.R.A. Governments.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-106-1A)
    Panel: The I.R.A. and Indian Culture, religion, and the arts.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-106-2A)
    Panel: The I.R.A. and Indian culture, religion, and the arts.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-201-A)
    James E. Officer speaks on termination.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-202-1A)
    Panel: Termination, 1945-1960. Moderated by Rupert Costo.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-202-2A)
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-203-1A)
    Panel: Undoing the I.R.A.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-203-2A)
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-204-1A)
    Panel: The Indian claims commission.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-204-2A)
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-205-1A)
    Panel: Relocation and other termination period programs and policies.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-205-2A)
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-206-1A)
    Panel: The impact of termination - yesterday and today.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-206-2A)
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-301-A)
    Phillip S. Deloria speaks on self-determination.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-302-1A)
    Panel: Self-determination, 1960-1976. Moderated by Alfonso Ortiz.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-302-2A)
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-303-1A)
    Panel: War on poverty: The expanded Federal presence in Indian life.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-303-2A)
    Panel: The war on poverty: The expanded Federal presence in Indian life.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-304-1A)
    Panel: Activism and Red Power.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-304-2A)
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-305-1A)
    Panel: Traditionalism and the Sol Tax.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-305-2A)
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-306-1A)
    Panel: Contracting under PL 638. Self-determination.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-306-2A)
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-401-A)
    W. Roger Buffalohead speaks on the I.R.A: The past and the future.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-402-1A)
    Panel: The I.R.A: The past and the future. Moderated by Phillip Deloria.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-402-2A)
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-403-1A)
    Panel: Tribal sovereignty: roots, expectations, and limits.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-404-A)
    Panel: Indian control of Indian resources.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-405-1A)
    Panel: The trust obligation.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-405-2A)
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-406-1A)
    Panel: What should Indians want? Advice to the President.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-406-2A)
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-501-A)
    Compilation of comments from evening film screening.
  - KUER and the Institute of the American West, 1983; Compact disc (Disc ISR-503-A)
    Floyd Westerman concert.
  - Hank Adams Interview, 1984 January 30; Compact disc (Disc ISR-701-1)
    Interviewed by K. MacKay.
  - Hank Adams Interview, 1983 August 21; Compact disc (Disc ISR-701-2)
  - Robert Bennett, 1984 January 30; Compact disc (Disc ISR-702)
    Interviewed by K. MacKay
  - Ramona Bennett, 1983 August 20; Compact disc (Disc ISR-703)
  - Lucy Cohen, 1984 February 02; Compact disc (Disc ISR-704)
    Interviewed by Ambler
  - Dr. Fred Eggan, 1983 August 18; Compact disc (Disc ISR-705-1)
    Interviewed by Greg Thompson
  - Dr. Fred Eggan, 1983 August 18; Compact disc (Disc ISR-705-1A)
    Interviewed by Thompson
  - Dr. Fred Eggan, 1983 August 18; Compact disc (Disc ISR-705-2)
  - Dr. Fred Eggan, 1983 August 18; Compact disc (Disc ISR-705-2A)
  - Dr. Fred Eggan, 1983 August 18; Compact disc (Disc ISR-705-3)
  - Dr. Fred Eggan, 1983 August 19; Compact disc (Disc ISR-705-3A)
  - Larry Echohawk, 1983 August 19; Compact disc (Disc ISR-706)
  - Lucille Echohawk, 1983 August 18; Compact disc (Disc ISR-707)
  - E. Reesman Fryer, 1983 August 18; Compact disc (Disc ISR-708-1)
    Interviewed by Alley and Tony G.
  - E. Reeseman Fryer, 1983 August 18; Compact disc (Disc ISR-708-2)
  - Tim Giago, undated; Compact disc (Disc ISR-709)
  - Celina Goolsby, 1983 August 19; Compact disc (Disc ISR-710)
  - Ladonna Harris, undated; Compact disc (Disc ISR-711)
  - Graham Holmes, 1983 August 16; Compact disc (Disc ISR-712)
  - Edward Johnson, 1983 August 20; Compact disc (Disc ISR-713-1)
    Interviewed by Alley
  - Edward Johnson, 1983 August 20; Compact disc (Disc ISR-713-2)
  - Helen Sanders, undated; Compact disc (Disc ISR-714)
  - Arthur Manning, 1983 August 18; Compact disc (Disc ISR-715)
  - Francis McKinley, 1983 August 16; Compact disc (Disc ISR-716)
    Interviewed by O'Neil and MacKay
  - Alexander McNabb, 1983 August 20; Compact disc (Disc ISR-717)
  - Philleo Nash, 1983 August 17; Compact disc (Disc ISR-718)
    Interviewed by Don Fixico and Thompson
  - Earl Old Person, undated; Compact disc (Disc ISR-719)
  - Gerald One Feather, 1983 August 17; Compact disc (Disc ISR-720)
    Interviewed by MacKay
  - Helen Peterson, 1983 August 18; Compact disc (Disc ISR-721-1)
  - Ben Reifel, undated; Compact disc (Disc ISR-722)
  - Dalee Sambo and Ted Katcheak, undated; Compact disc (Disc ISR-723)
  - Steve Unger, 1983 August 20; Compact disc (Disc ISR-728)
  - Charlotte Lloyd, 1983 August 17; Compact disc (Disc ISR-729)
  - Dave Warren, 1983 August 17; Compact disc (Disc ISR-730-1)
    Interviewed by Thompson and Alley
  - Dave Warren, 1983 August 17; Compact disc (Disc ISR-730-2)
  - Henrietta Whiteman, 1983 August 20; Compact disc (Disc ISR-732)
    Interviewed by Clark, Thomas, and Thompson
  - Gerald Wilkenson, undated; Compact disc (Disc ISR-733)
  - Charles Wilkinson, 1983 August 19; Compact disc (Disc ISR-734)
    Interviewed by Thompson and Clark
- MacKay interviews, 1980-1997
  - Elloise Bell, 1997 September 05; Compact disc (Disc MacKay-1)
    In this interview Elloise speaks of her participation in the IWI at the 10 year reunion.
  - Winny Barlow, 1980 May 07; Compact disc (Disc MacKay-2)
    In this interview Winny discusses her family history and personal background.
  - Joy Takiyama Hashimato, 1981 April 21; Compact disc (Disc MacKay-3)
    Personal experience with WYCA.
  - Helen Brown Jarmin, 1981 February 27; Compact disc (Disc MacKay-4)
    Mrs. Jarmin was the Executive Director of SLC WYCA. In this interview she speaks about her introduction and experience pertaining to the YWCA.
  - Carol Cordwell Maxin, 1985; Compact disc (Disc MacKay-5)
    President of the Utah Womens History Association lecture.
  - Gwen Stephens Hirshchman Hovey, undated; Compact disc (Disc MacKay-6)
    Mrs. Hovey discusses the history of Salt Lake City's YWCA and her experience with it.
  - Rose Sconviensa (sp?), 1985 May 16; Compact disc (Disc MacKay-7)
    Family history and personal background.
    Interviewed by K. MacKay and J. Tabish
  - O. Meredith Wilson lecture series: Dr. Lawrence Stone, 1981; Compact disc (Disc MacKay-8)
    Tanner lecture trust and department of history's fifth annual O. Meredith Wilson lecture series with speaker Dr. Lawrence Stone of Princeton University.
  - Women in Utah history, undated; Compact disc (Disc MacKay-9)
    Kathrine MacKay speaks on the role of women in the history of Utah. She includes excerpts from diaries, poems, and quotes from women of the nineteenth century as primary information.
  - Katey Dixon, undated; Compact disc (Disc MacKay-10)
    Ten year celebration of IWI and Ms. Dixons involvement with the IWI committee.
  - Dr. Reba Kiel, 1987 September 05; Compact disc (Disc MacKay-11)
    Events of IWI conference and Ms. Kiels involvement with the IWI.
  - Sharon Keigher, undated; Compact disc (Disc MacKay-12)
    Involvement with the IWI.
  - Meralee Carling Lada, 1987; Compact disc (Disc MacKay-13)
  - Ida Smith, undated; Compact disc (Disc MacKay-14)
    Involvement with Brigham Young University's Women Research Institute and the IWI.
- General Materials, undated
  - Western music, undated; Compact disc (Disc Western Music-1)
    Nine tracks of western music. Artist unknown.
  - Western music, undated; Compact disc (Disc Western Music-2)
  - Willis Thompson, undated; Compact disc (Disc Willis Thompson-1)
    Willis Thompson oral history interview used for Ute Tribe education.